{
    "subject": "Juana_Enr\u00edquez",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_II_of_Aragon",
    "human_readable": "Juana Enr\u00edquez is married to John II of Aragon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986318826675415,
            "question": "Was John II of Aragon married before Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.96879643201828,
            "question": "What was the significance of the marriage between Juana Enr\u00edquez and John II of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9445276856422424,
            "question": "What is John II of Aragon's relationship to Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.908314049243927,
            "question": "Who is Juana Enr\u00edquez married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7499755024909973,
            "question": "Did Juana Enr\u00edquez have any children with John II of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7012755870819092,
            "question": "Where did Juana Enr\u00edquez and John II of Aragon live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6657432913780212,
            "question": "What era did Juana Enr\u00edquez and John II of Aragon live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4715519845485687,
            "question": "Who was the King of Aragon during Juana Enr\u00edquez's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4434361755847931,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Juana Enr\u00edquez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.267045795917511,
            "question": "How is John II of Aragon remembered in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Juana Enr\u00edquez is married to John II of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_25530_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Juana Enr\u00edquez?",
            "html": "yago_25530_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the King of Aragon during Juana Enr\u00edquez's lifetime?",
            "html": "yago_25530_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era did Juana Enr\u00edquez and John II of Aragon live in?",
            "html": "yago_25530_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25530_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Juana Enr\u00edquez is married to John II of Aragon.\" For instance, in `67.txt`, it mentions Juana I, Queen of Castile and Le\u00f3n and Queen of Aragon as being born to Juan II, King of Aragon and his wife Juana Enriquez. Additionally, the document `30.txt` specifically states that \"the future spouses got betrothed \u2013 they took each other\u2019s hands \u2013 at Torrelobat\u00f3n, on 1 September 1444,\" indicating their marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}